Guide to the Brooklyn schools collection CBHM.0006
Center for Brooklyn History
- Series 2: Individual schools
  - Long Island University
    - Library Leaves newsletter, 1973 February (Box 7)
    - Brooklyn Center Guide, 1973 (Box 7)
    - Promotional booklets, 1978, 1995 (Box 7)
    - South Africa and Apartheid conference poster, 1986 (Folder Flat File)
    - Bridge Basis Program Multi-Media ARTifact, 1995, 1996 (Box 17)
    - Downtown and Upbeat newsletter, 2001, 2004 (Box 7)
  - Manual Training High School
    - Odd Times weekly, 1905 (Box 7)
    - Prospect yearbook, 1905-1960 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
      1905-1923, 1925-1927, January 1928, 1929-1942, January 1943, 1944-1960
      The January 1943 yearbook belonged to John A. "Jack" Watson and was the gift of Barbara Gliwa, 2025.
    - Manualite yearbook, 1911-1914 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - Commencement invitation, 1912 (Box 7)
    - Prospect journal, 1919-1921 (Box 7)
    - Blue Book, 1921 (Box 7)
    - Manual Anvil, 1921 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - Image of school building, circa early 20th century (Box 7)
    - John A. "Jack" Watson graduation portrait, January 1943 (Box 7)
      Gift of Barbara Gliwa, 2025.
  - Master School of Music
    - Annual reports, 1905, 1907-1908, 1909-1912 (Box 8)
    - Vocal department catalogs, 1908-1909, 1911-1912 (Box 8)
    - Benefit concert program, circa 1912-1913 (Box 8)
  - Maxwell Teachers Training College
    - Chalk Marks yearbook, 1929, January 1933 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  - Medgar Evers College
    - Commencement invitation and programs, 1972-1974 (Box 8)
    - Tieline faculty/staff newsletter, 1975-1976 (Box 8)
    - Adafi newspaper, March 21, 1977 (Box 15)
    - Event materials, 1979-1992 (Box 8)
    - Everybody's Caribbean magazine article, 1994 (Box 8)
    - Promotional brochures, undated (Box 8)
  - Messrs. Van Doren's Institute for Young Ladies
    - Catalog, 1828 (Box 8)
  - Middle School (M.S.) 136 Charles O. Dewey
    - Reflections yearbook, 1969-2013 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
      1969, 1971, 1972, 1975-1982, 1984-1987, 1992, 2000 -2008, 2010, 2011, 2013
    - Yearbooks, 2000, 2001, 2007, 2008, 2010, 2011 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - Commencement programs, 2003, 2008, 2019 (Box 8)
    - Yearbooks, 2005, 2013 (Box 8)
  - M.S. 340 North Star Academy
    - Commencement programs, 2014-2015 (Box 7)
  - M.S. 447 Math and Science Exploratory
    - Yearbooks, 2015-2016 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  - Midwood High School
    - Epilog yearbook, 1942-2001 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
      1942, 1943, January 1946, January & June 1947, June 1948, January 1949, 1950, June 1951, 1956, 1957, 1987, 1990, 2001
    - Patterns literary magazine, 1948 Spring (Box 8)
    - Bicentennial programs press release, 1976 (Box 8)
    - Sing programs, 1981 (Box 8)
      One program is for an inter-school Sing with Sheepshead Bay High School and Abraham Lincoln High School.
  - Mills College of Education
    - The Link yearbook, 1956-1958, 1960, 1961, 1964 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
      1956 copy gift of Mary Keyes.
  - Miss Dudley's Seminary for Young Ladies
    - Catalog, 1867-1868 (Box 8)
  - Miss Hall's School
    - Catalogs, 1891, 1899 (Box 8)
  - Miss Katherine L. Maltby's Home and School for Young Ladies
    - Catalogs, 1890-1891, 1894-1895, 1895-1896, 1897-1898, circa 1900 (Box 8)
  - Miss Round's School for Girls
    - Class souvenir, 1891 (Box 8)
    - Catalogs, 1893, 1897-1900, 1903, 1904, 1907 (Box 8)
    - Alumnae Association publications, 1897, 1899-1900, 1902-1903, 1905-1906 (Box 8)
    - Commencement program, 1907 (Box 8)
  - Miss Whitcomb's School for Young Ladies and Children
    - Catalog, 1887-1888 (Box 8)
  - The Misses Crawford's School for Boys and Girls
    - Catalogs, 1895-1896, 1897-1898, 1898-1899 (Box 8)
  - The Misses Peck School of Music
    - Catalog, 1898-1899 (Box 8)
  - Most Holy Trinity High School
    - Triad yearbook, 1957 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  - Nassau Institute
    - Catalog, 1886-1887 (Box 8)
  - National Academy of Beauty Culture
    - Poster, 1937 (Folder Flat File)
  - New Utrecht High School
    - The Comet literary magazine/yearbook, 1918-1943 (Box 8)
      The June 1935 issue was the gift of Kenneth Grunwald, 2025.
      1918, 1925, 1932, June 1935, June 1943.
    - Commencement programs, 1934, 1938, 1939 (Box 8)
    - Report card, 1935 (Box 8)
    - Comet yearbook, 1932-1968 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
      January 1932, January 1935, January 1936, 1938, 1939, June 1941, January 1942, January 1948, 1950, 1952, January 1953, 1957, 1965, 1968.
      1968 yearbook was the gift of Leslie Meyers Gordon, 2023.
  - New York Christian Academy
    - Fundraising letter, 1972 (Box 8)
    - Poster with class photograph, 1972 (Box 15)
  - New York City Community College
    - The Statement yearbook, 1965 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  - New York City Technical College (City Tech)
    - Pamphlet, circa 1980s (Box 8)
    - Event flyers, circa 1980s (Box 8)
    - Calendars of events, 1983-1986 (Box 8)
    - President's Report, 1984 (Box 8)
    - Bulletin, 1986 April (Box 8)
    - College News, 1986 Spring (Box 8)
  - Our Lady of Lourdes
    - Report cards, 1954-1955 (Box 8)
    - Autograph book, 1957 (Box 12)
    - Diploma and senior portraits, 1957 (Box 8)
  - Our Lady of Perpetual Help
    - Commencement programs, 1942, 1943 (Box 8)
  - Polytechinal Institute of Brooklyn
    - Polywog yearbook, 1887-1983 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
      1934 copy was the gift of Jeanne Torre.
      1887, 1898-1901, 1904, 1905, 1908, 1911, 1920, 1921, 1923, 1934, 1936, 1937, 1952, 1955, 1959, 1962, 1983.
  - Polytechnic Preparatory Country Day School
    - Polyglot yearbook, 1901-2012 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
      1901-1903, 1905, 1906, 1908-1911, 1913-1916, 1918-1921, 1923-1926, 1929-1937, 1938-1941, 1943-1946, 1948-1951, 1953-1956, 1958-1976, 1978-1981, 1983-1986, 1988-1991, 1993-2006, 2009-2012.
      The 1932 and 1937 yearbooks were the gift of Joan Goodfellow-Faircloth, 2025.
  - Prospect Heights High School
    - Cardinal literary magazine, circa 1960s (Box 9)
    - Cardinal yearbook, 1959-1964 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - Prospector journal, 1985 (Box 9)
    - "The Past We Visited" program, 1986 (Box 9)
    - The Brooklyn Caribbean Beat journal, 1987-1991 (Box 9)
  - Propect Heights School
    - Catalog, 1903 (Box 9)
  - Prospect Hill School
    - The Monitor, 1921-1924, 1930 (Box 9)
  - Prospect Park Institute
    - Catalog, 1888-1889 (Box 9)
  - Public School (P.S.) 1
    - Student photographs contact sheet, 1927 (Box 9)
    - John Silva report card and reward of merit, 1856, 1859 (Box 9)
      Gift of Mildred K. Blair in memory of Mrs. Flora Hall Bergstrom.
  - P.S. 3
    - United War Work "Victory Junior" certificate, 1918 (Box 9)
    - Progress magazine, 1916 (Box 9)
      A microfiche version is available in the library (Microfiche 50).
  - P.S. 5
    - Certificate, 1858 (Box 9)
  - P.S. 7
    - "History of Public School 7" by class 5-301, 1971-1972 (Box 9)
  - P.S. 10 The Peter Rouget School
    - 100 Years of Progress: The History of Public School No. 10, 1941 (Box 9)
    - Art fair program, 1980 (Box 9)
  - P.S. 13
    - Reward of merit, 1864 (Box 9)
      Gift of Miss Helen C. Doyle.
  - P.S. 15
    - Commencement programs, 1875, 1886, 1889 (Box 9)
    - Alumni reunion program, 1877 (Box 9)
  - P.S. 18
    - Edward Bush testimonial dinner materials, 1899, 1912 (Box 9)
  - P.S. 19
    - Commencement program, 1886 (Box 9)
  - P.S. 20
    - Reward of merit, 1864 (Box 9)
    - Plan for playground and sports courts, 1954 (Box 9)
  - P.S. 25
    - Commencement program, 1932 (Box 9)
  - P.S. 30
    - Commencement program, 1941 (Box 9)
  - P.S. 35
    - The Decatur magazine, 1922-1925 (Box 9)
    - The Decatur Torch newspaper, 1932 (Box 15)
  - P.S. 37
    - Edwin Hathaway report cards, 1898-1899 (Box 9)
  - P.S. 39
    - Rewards of merit, 1884 (Box 14)
    - Autograph book, 1943; 2022.021 (Box 12)
      Gift of David Doss, 2021.
  - P.S. 41
    - OREA report on Project Sail, 1988 (Box 9)
  - P.S. 44
    - Commencement program, 1914 (Box 9)
    - Class photograph, 1919 (Box 15)
      Gift of John Manbeck.
  - P.S. 45
    - Autograph book, 1920 (Box 12)
  - P.S. 46
    - Grade 2B class photograph, 1927 (Box 9)
  - P.S. 48
    - Impressions literary magazine, June 1974 (Box 10)
      Also includes an accompanying letter from the school.
      A microfiche version of this publication is available in the library (Microfiche 50).
  - P.S. 52
    - Edwin Hathaway report cards, 1901-1902 (Box 10)
  - P.S. 67
    - The Sixty-Seven Times newsletter, 1976 (Box 10)
  - P.S. 73
    - Commencement programs, 1912, 1964 (Box 10)
    - Shakespearean pageant program, 1916 (Box 10)
  - P.S. 77
    - Commencement program, 1898 (Box 10)
  - P.S. 87
    - Report cards, 1898-1899 (Box 10)
      Kate Rustin.
  - P.S. 89
    - Class photograph, 1935 January (Box 15)
  - P.S. 90
    - Commencement program and ticket, 1900 (Box 10)
  - P.S. 92
    - Commencement program, 1916 (Box 10)
  - P.S. 100
    - Class photograph, 1942; 2023.003 (Box 15)
      Gift of the estate of Anna Hendlin, 2023.
  - P.S. 103
    - The Clarion literary magazine, 1941 (Box 10)
  - P.S. 107
    - Centennial album, 1995 (Box 10)
  - P.S. 108 Arlington School
    - Graduation program, 1928 (Box 10)
  - P.S. 122
    - Autograph book, 1930 (Box 12)
  - P.S. 130
    - Student record sheets, 1911-1934 (Box 10)
      These records also cover time spent at other schools: P.S. 7, 19, 95, 119, 122, 129, 154, 171.
    - Class photograph, 1922 (Box 15)
      Gift of Judy Lowin.
  - P.S. 134
    - Class 6-3 photograph, 1956 April (Box 10)
      Gift of Catherine Flynn.
  - P.S. 135
    - Class photograph, 1928 June (Folder Flat File)
    - Class photograph, 1935 January (Box 15)
      Gift of Vicki Davis Miller, 2025.
  - P.S. 136
    - Commencement programs, 1907, 1913, 1914 (Box 10)
  - P.S. 139
    - Class photograph, 1917 (Folder Flat File)
      Gift of Lynn Washborne Williams.
    - The Messenger journal, 1938 (Box 10)
    - Bulletin, 1961-1973 (Box 10)
  - P.S. 143
    Located on Havemeyer Street between 6th and 7th Streets in Williamsburg, the building that was P.S. 143 is now part of Harry Van Arsdale, Jr. High School.
    - Class book, 1923; 2012.013 (Box 10)
      A seemingly handmade book with photos pasted in with handwritten captions as well as typewritten pages including a list of graduates.
  - P.S. 145
    - Class photographs, 1938, 1943 (Folder Flat File)
  - P.S. 152
    - Lecture series program, 1915 (Box 10)
  - P.S. 154 The Windsor School
    - The Gleam journal/yearbook, 1934, 1935; 2022.046 (Box 10)
      Gift of Shana F. Messing, 2019.
  - P.S. 155
    - Report card, 1952 (Box 10)
  - P.S. 161
    - Ruth Green diploma, 1937 (Box 10)
    - Report card, 1946 (Box 10)
    - Crown Heights Courier alumni newsletter, 1990-2000 (Box 10)
      Gift of Gail Levine.
  - P.S. 167
    - Commencement program, 1931 (Box 10)
  - P.S. 170
    - Autograph book, 1949 (Box 12)
  - P.S. 181
    - Susan Hayward letter to Florence Lillian Cahill, circa 1926, 1941 (Box 10)
      A copy of a 1941 letter from the actress Susan Hayward (nee Edythe Marrenner) to her former teacher at P.S. 181, Florence Lillian Cahill, recalling memories of her time at the school. Also included is a photograph of Hayward and a copy of a circa 1926 photograph of Cahill.
      Biographical note
      Florence Lillian Cahill was born in 1903 in Brooklyn. She was a teacher at P.S. 181 and later principal at P.S. 248 in Gravesend. She was married to Jesse B. Manbeck and their son John B. Manbeck became Brooklyn Borough Historian.
  - P.S. 193
    - Live Wire literary magazine/yearbook, 1942 January (Box 10)
    - Class photograph, 1939 (Box 15)
      Gift of Merle Weinstein, 2025.
      Donor's father Robert Feinberg is pictured fifth from right in third row from top (round glasses).
    - Class photograph, 1945 (Folder Flat File)
  - P.S. 194
    - Autograph book, 1938 (Box 20)
    - Report card, 1938 (Box 10)
  - P.S. 197
    - The Guardian parents association newsletter, 1973 (Box 10)
  - P.S. 201
    - Commencement program, 1926 January (Box 10)
  - P.S. 202
    - Commencement program, 1932 (Box 10)
  - P.S. 203 Floyd Bennett
    - Mary Gurrera diploma, 1936 June 26 (Box 10)
    - Wings yearbook, 1965 June; Opis, Scott (Box 10)
    - Media Day materials, 2005 (Box 10)
  - P.S. 206
    - Commencement program, 1929 (Box 10)
  - P.S. 214
    - Commencement program, 1936 (Box 10)
    - Class photograph, circa 1936 (Box 10)
  - P.S. 216
    - Parents Association Bulletin, June 1969 (Box 10)
  - P.S. 219
    - Parent Teacher Bulletin, 1960, 1962 (Box 10)
  - P.S. 222
    - Commencement program, 1935 (Box 10)
  - P.S. 230
    - 50th anniversary booklet, 1981 (Box 10)
  - P.S. 231
    - New York magazine article excerpt, 1980 (Box 10)
    - Theater program, 1995 (Box 10)
  - P.S. 233
    - Commencement program, 1939 (Box 10)
  - P.S. 238
    - Commencement program, 1932 (Box 10)
  - P.S. 314 Luis Munoz Marin
    - Yearbooks, 1990-2002, 2004, 2005 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - Dual Language Gifted Academy magazine, 1994 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  - P.S. 371
    - Exhibition flyer, 2007 (Box 10)
  - P.S. 396
    - Dedication flyer, 1969 (Box 10)
  - P.S. 506 School of Journalism and Technology
    - Be the Difference yearbook, 2014-2015 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  - Rabbinical Seminary of America
    - Promotional materials, 2008 (Box 10)
  - Roosa School of Music
    - Programs, 1957-1984 (Box 10)
      Gift of Mrs. Samuel Brody, President of the Board of the school, 1974.
  - Saint (St.) Agnes Seminary
    - Diploma, 1980 (Box 11)
      Includes names and photographs of the graduating seniors.
    - The Agnesian yearbook, 1947 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  - St. Ambrose School
    - School reunion DVD, 2007; 2008.007 (Box 11)
  - St. Angela Hall Academy
    - Commencement programs, 1967, 1968, 1970, 1971 (Box 11)
    - Dance festival program, 1970 (Box 11)
  - St. Ann's School
    - St. Ann's Church education committee notes and correspondence, 1964 (Box 11)
    - Auction flyer, 1967 (Box 15)
    - Yearbook, 1987, 2005, 2006 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - "A History of 129 Pierrepont Street" by Max Greenebaum, 1988 (Box 11)
    - Saint Ann's School: An Unofficial History 1965-2015 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
      2 copies.
    - Saint Ann's Ram newspaper, 2023-2025 (Box 15)
      October 10, 2023; May 17, 2025.
  - St. Augustine's Diocesan High School
    - Lance yearbook, 1938, 1942, 1953, 1954, 1956-1968 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - Commencement program, 1968 (Box 10)
  - St. Barbara's Diocesan High School
    - Promotion exercises program, 1947 January; Barone, Rita G., -2021 (Box 10)
    - The Gleam newspaper, 1947 January; Barone, Rita G., -2021 (Box 10)
  - St. Bartholomew School
    - Diploma and senior portraits, 1969 (Box 10)
  - St. Catherine's Hall
    - Catalog, 1900 (Box 10)
  - St. Edmund Preparatory High School
    - Canterburian yearbook, 2002 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - Commencement materials, 2012 (Box 10)
  - St. Francis College
    - Commencement programs, 1888, 1914, 1967, 1968, 1973, 1974 (Box 11)
    - Informational booklet by Kings County Trust Co., 1957 (Box 11)
    - Franciscan yearbook, 1957, 1958 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - Development materials, circa 1960 (Box 11)
    - Development information packet, circa 1960 (Box 15)
    - Outreach materials, circa 1960 (Box 11)
    - Evening session programs, circa 1960 (Box 11)
    - Event materials, 1966, 1996-2010 (Box 11)
  - St. Francis Preparatory
    - San Fran yearbook, 1946 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - A Little Portion literary journal, 1961, 1962 (Box 11)
    - Annual concert programs, 1967, 1968 (Box 11)
  - St. Francis Xavier
    - Gateway yearbook, 1957, 1958, 1959 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - Pin for graduating class, 1960 (Box 11)
      Gift of Adriane Ruggiero, 2024.
    - The Maelstrom literary magazine, 1963 (Box 11)
  - St. James' Commercial School
    - Commencement materials, 1887 (Box 11)
  - St. John's College
    - Promotional materials, 1908, 1910, 1929 (Box 11)
    - Catalogue, 1925-1926 (Box 11)
  - St. John's Prep
    - Prep Shadows yearbook, 1941, 1942, 1959-1961, 1964-1966 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - Prep Powwow literary magazine, 1942 June
    - Senior night photographs, 1948 (Box 11)
    - Thanksgiving football game program, 1945 (Box 11)
      Game played against Brooklyn Prep.
    - Prep Alumni Bulletin, April 1949 (Box 11)
    - Red Owl newspaper, March 14, 1947 (Box 15)
    - Felt pennant, circa late 1940s (Folder Flat File)
  - St. John's University
    Some yearbooks were the gift of Edwin B. Hewes, Mary Sparacio, and Marilyn Horwin.
    - The Vincentian yearbook, 1937, 1948, 1957 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - Diamond Jubilee booklet, 1945 (Box 16)
    - 25th anniversary dinner booklet, 1950 (Box 16)
    - Epitome literary magazine, 1951 June (Box 16)
    - The Indian yearbook, 1951, 1952 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - Commencement materials, 1953 (Box 16)
    - Promotional booklet, 1954 (Box 16)
    - Convocation program, 1955 (Box 16)
    - Catalogs, 1956-1957, 1958-1959 (Box 16)
    - Tomahawk yearbook, 1968 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - School of Law
      - Res Genstae yearbook, 1941, 1953, 1958, 1961 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
        School of Law.
      - The Liber yearbook, 1931-1932 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
        Schools of Law and Arts and Sciences.
    - College of Business Administration
      - Closing Entry yearbook, 1943 (Box 11)
      - Closing Entry yearbook, 1931-1941, 1949-1963 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
        School of Accounting, Commerce, and Finance.
    - Teachers College
      - The Warrior yearbook, 1951, 1954 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  - St. Joseph High School
    - Christmas assembly, 1970 (Box 16)
  - St. Joseph's College
    - Footprints yearbook, 1928, 1937, 1939, 1962-1965, 1967, 1968 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
      The 1967 and 1968 yearbooks were the gift of the Pendleton Fund in memory of James Thorpe Pendleton and Frederick Starr Pendleton, Jr.
    - Catalog, 1954-1956 (Box 16)
    - Exhibition materials, 1979, circa 2010 (Box 16)
    - Promotional materials, circa 1980s (Box 16)
      Includes pamphlet for Dillon Center Preschool.
    - Inner Sanctum newsletter, 1984 (Box 16)
  - St. Joseph's Commercial High School
    - Commencement photograph, 1951 (Folder Flat File)
    - Parmentier yearbook, 1956, 1957 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  - St. Leonard's High School
    - Leonardian yearbook, 1959 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  - St. Mary's Hospital School of Nursing
    - Yearbook, 1952 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  - St. Michael's Diocesan High School
    - The Michaelog newspaper, 1956 (Box 15)
  - St. Nicholas Commercial High School
    - Dominicanette yearbook, 1951-1953 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  - St. Ruth International Biblical Institute
    - Reopening program, 1968 (Box 16)
  - St. Saviour High School
    - Yearbook, 1952 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - Thabor yearbook, 1958-1961, 1970-1973 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  - St. Saviour's Parochial School
    - Student identification tag, circa 1940s (Box 16)
      Gift of Rose Marie Sinnot, 2017.
  - Samuel J. Tilden High School
    - Diploma, 1935 (Box 16)
    - Classic yearbook, 1933-2010 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
      The June 1938 yearbook was a transfer from the Whitfield-Murray Historical Society from the estate of Allen and Adele Finkel, 2024. The 1986-2010 yearbooks were the gift of Barbara Ferington and formerly owned by Clarence H. Kay, a teacher at the school.
      1933, 1935-1938, 1940, January 1941, 1942, 1943, 1944, 1946, 1950, 1967, 1969, 1986, 1994, 1998, 2004, 2005, 2009, 2010
    - Arista tenth anniversary booklet, 1940 (Box 16)
    - Commencement programs, 1940, 1943, 1950, 1967, 1983 (Box 16)
      The 1983 program was the gift of Barbara Ferington and formerly owned by Clarence H. Kay, a teacher at the school.
    - Scholastic credit certificate, 1941 (Box 16)
    - Concert ticket, 1966 (Box 16)
    - Caravan literary magazine, 1983-1984 (Box 16)
      These two items were the gift of Barbara Ferington and formerly owned by Clarence H. Kay, a teacher at the school.
    - Alumni newsletter, 1988-1999 (Box 16)
    - Student planner, 2004-2005 (Box 16)
      This item was the gift of Barbara Ferington and formerly owned by Clarence H. Kay, a teacher at the school.
  - Sarah J. Hale Vocational High School
    - Mannequin yearbook, 1959 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - Commencement programs, 1960-1963, 1968-1971 (Box 16)
    - Promotional pamphlet, circa 1960s (Box 16)
    - Text on Sarah J. Hale, circa 1960s (Box 16)
    - Hail Horizons yearbook, 1960-1963, 1976-1982 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
      The 1976-1982 yearbooks were the gift of Barbara Ferington and formerly owned by Clarence H. Kay, a teacher at the school.
  - Sheepshead Bay High School
    - Topaz yearbook, 1961-1967, 1974, 1991 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  - Shore Road Academy
    - Catalogs, 1929-1931 (Box 16)
  - Simon F. Rothschild Junior High School
    - Commencement programs and ticket, 1973-1974 (Box 16)
  - South Brooklyn Female Seminary
    - Catalog, 1864 (Box 16)
  - Sunset Park Neighborhood School of Music
    - Correspondence and ephemera, 1981-1985 (Box 16)
  - SUNY Urban Center
    - Pamphlets, circa 1970s (Box 16)
  - Thomas Jefferson High School
    - Pieces of Eight yearbook, 1927 June (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - Soundings yearbook, 1928 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - Flashes yearbook, 1929 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - Etchings yearbook, 1930 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
    - Flambeau yearbook, June 1934 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
      Transfer from the Whitfield-Murray Historical Society from the estate of Allen and Adele Finkel, 2024.
    - Diploma, 1937 (Box 16)
    - Commencement programs, 1937-1938, 1941, 1943, 1944 (Box 16)
    - Farcity show program, 1938 (Box 16)
    - Aurora yearbook, 1937-1986 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
      1937, June 1938, January 1940, 1941, June 1942, January 1943, 1944, 1945, June 1947, 1949-1950, 1960, 1961, 1963, 1986
    - Perry Goldstein materials, 1941-1944 (Box 16)
      Service rating card, dance invitation, five report cards and one fabric patch.
      See also Goldstein's materials from J.H.S. 149 East New York.
    - Shirley Rapp materials, 1943 (Box 16)
      Includes diploma, senior prom ticket, report card, and honor card.
    - Mildred Groman materials, 1944 (Box 16)
      Intramural letter, diploma, commencement gown and collar receipt, and metal pendant.
    - Spring Festival flyer, 1970 (Box 16)
  - Torah Academy High School
    - Solomon Sandberg letter, 1988; 2022.052 (Box 16)
      Gift of Solomon Jacob Sandberg.
  - Training School for Teachers
    - Commencement program, 1896 (Box 16)
  - Tri-Borough Elementary Schools of the Northeastern Conference Seventh-Day Adventists
    - Commencement programs, 1967-1969, 1971, 1973, 1974 (Box 16)
  - Trinity High School
    - Commencement program, 1920 (Box 16)
  - Union Missionary Training Institute
    - Catalogue, 1915-1916 (Box 16)
  - Walt Whitman School
    - The City Record journal/yearbook, 1916 (Box 16)
  - William E. Grady Vocational-Technical High School
    - Encore, 1964 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  - William H. Maxwell Vocational High School
    - Crystal yearbook, 1970, 1973, 1993 (Volume Library gallery shelf)
  - Yeshiva of Flatbush
    - Bulletin newsletter, 1969 (Box 16)
  - Yeshiva Ohel Moshe
    - Press release, 1951 (Box 16)